besthometreadmill.co.za 2013-12-03

# Privacy Policy | Holistic Gym Systems | Miles Harrop

### We take your privacy seriously. 

This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. See this privacy policy primer to learn more about privacy policies in general.

## Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, www.holisticgym.co.za uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

## Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. This list of web browser privacy management links may also be useful.

## Contact Information

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to [miles.harrop@holisticgym.co.za](mailto:miles.harrop@holisticgym.co.za "Click to Email Us") for further clarification.

#### www.HolisticGym.co.za 

I am a fitness and wellness industry expert.

   I write and research on all areas of mental and physical wellness, focusing on helping people achieve their fitness, physical and mental transformation goals.

   I have assisted clients throughout South Africa in setting up functional home gyms, corporate gyms and profitable commercial gyms.

   I’m also an NLP coach with a Hypnotherapy, Motivation and Coaching practice My courses are available throughout South Africa in group training, corporate training or on a one on one basis. In addition, these courses are also available in a download format.  

   Call +27 (0) 71 863 7398 now for a quick discussion on how I can help you or your business.
